(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T08:29:42.369359",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Cut one.
I'm Gawr Gura, and you're watching Gura Channel!
And I can't get me in here, hahaha!
おはようございます！どうも、サメです！
Good morning! Hello, I'm a shark!
We're going to add some blue here for my hair.
We're going to go accuracy just 'cause it's me and I know how to draw myself the most, I would say.
Oh dear, after I've just messed up. That's fine.
Hola amigos! Como? Como te llamo?
Do you gusta nacho fries? Gusta es nacho fries?
Me gusta.
Me gusta. Ja, ja, ja...
Hello everyone!
Welcome to the very first episode of
Holo Live Trivia with yours truly
Gura
There are currently no plans for a second edition.
today we have some wonderful guests shall we meet them I think we shall
Hello guests!
ぺこらでーす！マリンでーす！
Pekora desu! Marine desu!
And we have one more special guest.
いなでーす！いなでーす！
Ina desu! Ina desu!
ホワイとぬいぐるみフォーラム、ふふふふ。
Howaito ningurumi forumu, hu hu hu hu.
Yes, I'll be joining you today, kindly lead you through the program.
Let's get started right away, shall we? 始めましょうか？お願いします！
Let's get started right away, shall we? Hajimemashou ka? Onegaishimasu!
So, in order to learn more about Hololive, we put this show together...
called Hololive Intro Quiz!
イントルドン！
Intro-don!
Yes, we'll play the intro to some of the Hololive songs, fate short or not.
And you'll have to guess what it is, Gura.
And we'll have Pekora-senpai and Senpai...
help you kind of guess what the song is. Okay, okay, Senpai-senpai. わからない！
help you kind of guess what the song is. Okay, okay, Senpai-senpai. Wakarusenai!
そうそうそう。
So, so, so.
All right. So with that, let's play a song.
たどん？
Dadun?
たとぅん！Easy game! Easy easy easy easy easy.
Tatun! Easy game! Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
Easy easy. あ。
Easy, easy. Ah.
Stellar-Stellar! すいせいせんぱい、星街すいせい！
Stellar-Stellar! Suisei-senpai, Hoshimachi Suisei!
だって僕は星だから
Datte boku wa hoshi dakara
stellar stellar
きっと君はもう気づいていた
kitto kimi wa mou kidzuiteita
僕の心の奥で描いた
boku no kokoro no oku de egaita
That's right! かわいい！
That's right! Kawaii!
Nice. それ、いかが？長かった？
Nice. Sore, ikaga? Nagakatta?
All right, all right. How about next song?
Oh, next song?
はい！あれ？は？
Hai! Hare? Ha?
Violet by Ninomae Ina'nis!
花が寝る夜 波に映った星
Hana ga neru yoru nami ni utsutta hoshi
うねる月が足をおすぐる
uneru tsuki ga ashi wo osuguru
Correct! ご本人！ご本人登場！
Correct! Gohon'in! Gohon'in toujou!
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
It's been, it's been too easy right now. I wonder if I'll have some difficult questions.
Get the challenge.
All right, all right. もっと短くしていいし。選抜next challenge.
All right, all right. Motto mijikaku shite iishi. Senbatsu next challenge.
Number three!
Ah! 声でわかった！
Ah! Koe de wakatta!
Okay? Okay.
Do you know this one?
Hai, minna know that voice anywhere.
あくあせんぱい！あくあ色ぱレット！
Aqua-senpai! Akuiro Palette!
何をしていても不器用でなにかとミスばっち
Nani o shite ite mo fukuyuu de nani ka to misubacchi
ダメダメな私だけでできることがあるの
Dame dame na watashi dake de dekiru koto ga aru no
すごい！
Sugoi!
Very, very good, very, very good. All right, all right. Let's see if the next one is even more challenging.
Let's go.
Ah! これは難しいか？声がなかったからわかるかな？
Ah! Kore wa muzukashii ka? Koe ga nakatta kara wakaru kana?
Okay, Gura.
That was a really hard line.
I can feel it. Can I feel it?
ヒント！ヒント！
Hinto! Hinto!
手を上げて！
Te wo agete!
Nice! Next!
Blue Clapper! Hololive Idol Project!
地球を上げて clapper head!
Chikyuu wo agete clapper head!
手を上げて clapper head!
Te wo agete clapper head!
You got them all right.
Last line! Last one! Last one! Last one!
Hit me.
ぺこら先輩、ぺこらのぶる…
Pekora-senpai, Pekora no buru...
ぺこらんだぶれいん！兎田ぺこら！
Pekorandabu reine! Usada Pekora!
No, no! no no!
ぺこらんだむぶれいん！ / 兎田ぺこら
Pekorandombrain! / Usada Pekora
That was actually all the songs we had, and Gura you got them all right!
いえーい！ナイスサポート！ナイスサポート！
Yay! Nice support, nice support!
All right, all right, let's move on to the next program, shall we?
Alright, alright. Let's move on to the next program, shall we?
次のプログラムは…どどん！hololive Member Posing Challenge!
Next program is... hololive Member Posing Challenge!
ポージング！
Posing!
You will see a picture of a hololive member. Strike a pose that you associate with them!
Easy game.
So I'll give you short countdown, and you'll have to make the pose of the holomem.
Are you ready?
Okay!
All right!
Alright!
First member is… おっ、誰だ、はっ？
First member is... Who is it, huh?
キアラ！キアラちゃん！キアラ！
Kiara! Kiara-chan! Kiara!
All right! Ready? Ready? Ready?
Alright. Ready? Ready?
オッケー、オッケー、オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay, okay.
3, 2, 1!
キアラ！キアラ！待って待って！え、違うやろ。それ何すか？
Kiara! Kiara! Wait, wait. You're striking a pose for Kiara, but...
チキン！チキン！チキン！チキン！
Fried chicken! Fried chicken! Fried chicken!
チキン持ってんじゃねぇ！
Fried chicken, you got that right!
だろ、ふつうのチキンのヘッド。オッケー、オッケー。
That's just a chicken head. Okay, okay.
二人ともKFPじゃん。まりんせんぱいとぐらは？
Both of you are striking a pose for KFP!
キッケリキー！キッケリキー！
Kikkeri ki! Kikkeri ki!
お、ベビー！Yes, exactly.
Oh, baby! Yes, exactly.
Alright, alright.
All right, all right.
If I have to give a point… ああ、チキン！チキン！あ、ごめんぺこら先輩、ごめん。
If I have to give a point... I'm sorry, Pekora-senpai. I'm sorry.
あ、ごめん。でも、ぐらはまりんせんぱいとKFP اینجا行くわ。
Gura has to go with Marine-senpai and KFP here.
チキン持ってんじゃねぇよ！オッケー、オッケー。オッケー、みんなもう一回ね。オッケー、みんなにもう一度。
Fried chicken, you got that right! Okay, okay. I'll give you another chance.
もう一度チャンス。All right! Next number!
I'll give you another chance. Alright, next number!
おっ、誰だ？
Who is it, huh?
All right, all right. Let's see, let's see if you guys got this.
Alright, alright. Let's see, let's see if you guys got this.
これじゃねぇ？カリオペちゃんね。カリオペ。
Calliope? Calliope-chan!
All right. 3, 2, 1, don!
Alright. 3, 2, 1, don!
おー、なんだこれ？なんだこれ？Yo-yo、RAPAH!
What is that? What is that? Yo-yo rappah!
Kelly's rapping pose!
まりん、おっ、これ鎌持ってるんですけど。
Marine, wait, are you holding a scythe?
鎌持って、あ、確かに持っている。
You're holding a scythe? Ah, true. You're holding it.
She's holding her scythe. Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
All right, all right. I'm gonna have to go with Marine-senpai and Gura here. Yes, all right. Wow.
All right, all right. I'm going to go with Marine-senpai and Gura here. Yes, all right. Wow.
How about the next one?
おっ？どどん！
Who is it? Don!
あ、ら！ぐら！オッケー、オッケー。
Gura? Gura! Okay, okay.
オッケー、ready? ぐらか…
Okay, ready? Gura ka...
3, 2, 1, go!
しゃーく！
Shark!
おえ、これ！あてには。しゃーく！
Oh, wait. Is she a shark?
しゃくしゃく…しゃくしゃくって何のこと？お前のは。しゃくしゃくって言って。
Shakshuka? What are you talking about? Shark!
しゃーく！
Shark!
どう？ぐらはしゃーく！Correlation?
What? Gura is a shark. Correlation?
Yes, alright. I'm gonna have to go with Pekora-senpai and Gura, but I mean, Brownie points for Marine.
Yeah. I'm going to have to go with Pekora-senpai and Gura, but I mean, Brownie points for Marine.
しゃくしゃくって、しゃくしゃくっている、しゃくしゃく。
Shakshuka? What are you talking about? Shakshuka.
おー、りら、やめな。おー、りら、やめな。
Ollie, yummy! Ollie, yummy!
Okay, next number!
Alright, next number!
おっ？にあ、にのちょ？
Who is it? Nina-cho!
オッケー、オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay, okay.
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
難しいな、ちょっと。ちょっと難しいぷこだな。おっ、誰が、オッケー、オッケー。
It's a bit difficult. It's a bit difficult, isn't it?
I'll be, I'll be the judge for this one, okay.
All right, 3, 2, 1, go!
Alright, 3, 2, 1, go!
え？え？ぐらでしょ？ぐら？
Gura? Gura?
ね、寝ちゃったよ。
She went to sleep!
Hey, book and pen, book and pen.
オッケー。ぺこら先輩、どんなポーズですか？
Pekora-senpai, what pose is that?
Book and pen! イラストー！ぴくしゃ、ぴくしゃん！
Book and pen. Illustrator! Pek-chan, Pek-chan!
まりんは？Marine、many, many tentacles. あ、tentacles! 多くのtentacles。
Marine? Many, many tentacles. Tentacles. Ah, tentacles.
ああ、オッケー。andぐら、あれ、ぐらでん？ぐら？
Okay. And Gura... Gura didn't... Gura?
I'm taking a nap.
昼寝してた、昼寝。昼寝！そう！
She's taking a nap! Nap! Nap!
あー、オッケー、あ。
Okay.
オッケー。なあ、どれ、どれが一番、Many tentacles、many tentacles.
Okay. Which one... Which one is the best? Many tentacles, many tentacles.
I have to go with Gura this. や、Gura!
I have to go with Gura this... Gura!
待てない、I can't wait to this.
I can't wait to this.
お昼寝が…すいな、クラスに2回が足りなかった。
A nap. She didn't have enough sleep.
Wow, wow, wow, ok.
Wow, wow, wow, okay.
How about the next one? Marine's... おー、オッケー、オッケー。
How about the next one? Marine's... Oh, okay, okay.
あめちゃん。オッケーですね。あめちゃん、オッケーです。
Ame-chan. Okay.
3, 2, 1, go!
ちょ、手が…手が写ってない。ちょっとマリンの…あれ？これ、ぐれ、え？
Wait, your hands... Your hands aren't showing, Marine.
指が…指が見えてないから！え、それないや、それ。
Your fingers... Your fingers aren't showing!
これは虫眼鏡をやっているでしょうか？
This is... She's probably doing a magnifying glass.
声聞こえてる？
Can you hear my voice?
声聞こえないなら、こ、こうです。
If you can't, do it like this.
あれ？ぐらちゃんとまりお同じなんか？
Huh? Are Gura and Marine doing the same one?
同じ、同じ、虫眼鏡。
Same, same. Magnifying glass.
二人分かってない、分かってない！
You two don't get it, you don't get it!
え、FPSなら、あめちゃんといけるから！
If it's FPS, I can do it with Ame!
虫眼鏡？FPS？あ、先輩。
Magnifying glass? FPS? Ah, senpai.
あめちゃんあまり使ってないんですよね、これ。
Ame doesn't really use this, do you?
あ、でもちょっと、っていうことはFPSか！
Ah, wait, does that mean it's FPS?
お飾り虫眼鏡、お飾り虫眼鏡。
Just a decorative magnifying glass.
触れ合うでも、確かに。どのポーズ？
Touching hands, true. Which pose?
Vergil.
ああ、デビルメイクライね！はいはい。
Ah, Devil May Cry! Right, right.
あ、デビルメイクライ！キュートポーズ！
Ah, Devil May Cry! Cute pose!
I can't choose. I can't choose.
あ、ドローこれ、ドロー。あ、ドロー！
Ah, draw this one, draw. Ah, draw!
First of all. 難しいよ。
First of all. It's difficult.
あ、もうすぐ分かるよ。
Ah, you'll figure it out soon.
なんだっけ、なんとかメトロノーム。
What was it, some kind of metronome.
まるでマリオネット、キモムーブ。
It's like a marionette, creepy movement.
うえ！かわいい！これもさ、I can't choose!
Ugh! Cute! This one too, I can't choose!
まっすぐメトロノームにしましょう。
Let's go with straight metronome.
1つしかないわ。よし、見よう見よう、オッケー。
There's only one. Alright, let's see, okay.
おい待てお前、何回完結ばっかしてんだ、ジャビットテール。
Hey, wait a minute, how many times are you gonna do Rabbit Tail?
うさぎぺこでしょ。お前のケツ出さねえんだよ。
It's Usada Pekora, right? You're not showing your butt.
ぐらそれ、ぐら何？あ、ぶんぶんちゃ。あれ、カリオペと一緒じゃねえか。
Gura, what's that? Ah, boom boom cha. Hey, isn't that the same as Calliope?
あ、じゃあ船長も同じじゃないですか。え、これ違う！これはラビットテール、ラビットテールってめこやったことねえめこだもん！
Ah, then Senpai is the same too? Eh, this is different! This is Rabbit Tail, Pekora's never done Rabbit Tail before!
どれ？本人いるんですけど、ちょっとあれはちょっと、え、嘘でしょ！そんなことしないよ！え、するペコでしょ。
Which one? The person herself is here, but that's... Eh, no way! I wouldn't do that! Eh, you definitely do that.
でも、ぶんぶんちゃもっとかっこいい。かっこいい。そうそうそう。
But boom-boom-cha is cooler. Cooler. That's right. Very cool.
でも実際のぶんぶんちゃはこんなんじゃなくて、もっとこんな感じじゃ… お待ちかね。
But the real boom-boom-cha isn't like this, it's more like... Wait for it.
ラスト！ドンドン！おねがいします！頼みました！
Last! Ba-dum! Please! I'm counting on you!
あ、やばい！足がまりにす、足がまりにす！揃った！揃った！やった！やった！
Ah, oh no! Feet are matching, feet are matching! They matched! They matched! Yay! Yay!
Yes, well, that'll be it for all the pose games.
よくできました。楽しかった。
Good job. That was fun.
Let's go to the next show, which is... I'm going to get naked.
Now that we're in the air, I'd like to direct your attention to the safety instructions in front of you.
Should we find ourselves in a...
If the plane's going down, tuck your head between your knees. Whoa!
It's just turbulence. Don't worry.
about it.
It's like watching an anime.
Look down between your toes,
fellow earthling, what do you see?
Is it brown?
Is it mushy?
Is it dry?
This is called dirt.
Do you know how many organisms live inside the dirt?
Dirt.
As my mom used to say, dirt don't hurt.
Dang, it really tingles.
Oh, hey.
Didn't see you there.
Want to take a tour inside my bedroom?
You do?
Cool. All right, let's go.
Follow me, this way.
Actually, we're going to check out my gamer PC first.
You want to see how cool it is?
Check that baby out!
That's got eight billion cores.
Did you know that?
It's pretty cool. Yeah, I know.
Did I build it myself? Of course I did.
Gura PC Gamer, Gura.
Anyway, look at my sofa.
I spend ungodly amounts of time on this sofa right here, could you believe that? I bet you could.
Um, if you're asking yourself, Gura, where is the Ina pillow?
Um, it's currently in the wash.
It's, uh, going it's coming back. It's in the wash.
Don't speculate.
Okay, now I want to show you my...
Fish tank! My e-fish tank.
Full of scrumdiddlyumptious ebi and...
For those of you that would like to join the fish tank after the end of today's, uh, program, there's going to be a form you can fill out and you have to sign. It's like a health waiver, but it's permanent for the rest of your lives.
Oh, there's my box of stuff too.
Well, my multiple boxes of stuff actually, including I actually have no idea what's in those.
But my trident's there. Uh, it's charging.
Neptune said never to touch a charging trident
because it messes with the power imbalances.
I don't know what that means, but I didn't ask him to expand on it.
My clothes.
Look at that. They look like they're made of paper.
That's because I used an iron for the first time and I have no idea how to use an ironing board, but I think that looks all right because there's no wrinkles in it.
Okay, and now you want to see my table?
It's a table, full of stuff. There's panties in this drawer.
Oh, that's a photo of me, isn't it great?
Uh, let's pretend I didn't say that.
Anyway, there's a AC control 'cause like it's sweaty at night, and then there's a fish tank that's also empty because...
I eat everything inside of it.
That is my midnight snack. You have a mini fridge, I have a fish tank.
So, uh, potato potado. Tomato tomato.
Uh, you want to see this? Check this out!
Gura camp!
Oh, we got, uh, Kiara!
Of course we have Gura.
Don't worry, we have Calli, Mori, Yuyu.
We have, uh, Ninomae Ina'nis, wa.
And then we have, uh, Amelia Watson.
And we have a little car.
Tell me, yeah, oh, I see.
Doesn't it really cool? Look.
Feet.
Let's take a closer look at these plushies, shall we?
Start with me.
Don't mo, show me desu.
It's me, small Gura, small and tiny.
I can take Gura by the rump.
Shaker, shaker, shake all their wintry money out.
No, Gura, stop, what are you doing to me, Gura?
Cute! Don't we look alike?
Tease.
And then we have, uh, Takanashi Kiara!
Kiara.
I feel like shipping Kiara. Kiara of this saying with somebody else who she really likes.
Avisay, kickidy kick!
Could it be?
Calliope Mori, it's me, your boy, Calli, Calli... bumps and, oh.
Kyo... Kyo, wait!
I'm Kiara!
Kiara, where are you? What are you doing here?
Calli!
Oh, yummy!
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch...
You get the idea.
You get the idea, don't you?
I'll put you back here.
And then we'll go ahead and we'll tag...
Ame, Ina, what so many nanisels are?
What's their ship name called? I'm sure you guys remember.
InAme.
This is Ame, this is Ina.
And then it'll ch-ch-ch-ch-ch...
Watson.
Dummy.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch...
Oh, sorry girls.
Anyway, let's say goodbye to Gumbus.
Gumbus, Gumbus, Gumbus, Gumbus!
Look! Cute, now?
Oh, do you want to see this?
Dun!
Who's going to go for a fun ride today, Gumba?
Broom, broom.
Yo! Oosah!
Not bad, Gumbus, for someone who can't drive, wouldn't you say?
I would say, girl.
I know.
Anyway, is there anything you'd like to say to the people?
It's time for you to leave. You've overstayed your welcome. Girl, you can't say that to the guests, they're here to see you.
Oh... Thank you for coming today and checking out my bedroom. I'll see you again real soon.
Kiss the... Kiss the shark. Kiss the shark.
Okay, it's time for you to go. Goodbye! Goodbye! Goodbye!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Goodbye! Boom!
Driving performed by professional(?) on a closed course
Shark May Goob / Available on the GawrBox (*not a real game lol)
ほらほらまた始まった お得意の自己弁護言い訳「でもね」「だって」
C'mon, c'mon, we're about to start it up, so drop your self defenses, they're just excuses. “But hey”, “That said…”
ほらほらまた始まった ごめん！からのおっきすのパターンって感じ？安易
C'mon, c'mon we're gonna start it up, sorry! my kisses give a pattern to your face can't you see? Easy…
“いつかアタシだけ” そんな夢見たこともあったけど
“Someday you'll be the only one”, but after all that time that I've dreamt,
寂しい時だけ電話して もううんざりだわ！
you'll only keep me around when you're feeling lonely -- don't keep me waiting like that!
全然アタシに興味ないじゅん キミが好きなのは自分 でしょ(Yeah!)
Although you're not at all interested in me, i wonder if you really only love yourself (Yeah!)
やっぱりアタシに興味ないじゅん その話もう聞き飽きたわ
Totally, you're not at all interested in me, but I've grown tired of that dumb fairytale,
そもそもだいだいアタシに興味ないじゅん そーやってまた誤魔化して… (もう!)
Really really, definitely you're not at all interested in me, as the gambling cheater says… (More!)
be my boy わがまま すぎるbaby 抱きしめてよね!
Be my boy, you're really quite greedy baby so give me your sweet embrace!
ホントキミはしょーもないな 甘いアタシ「そーもないな」
Guess I really don't know who you are yet, that sweet me “is still waiting for the main event”
泣いたって行かないでって言ったって変わりゃしないや!
Crying out, you still haven't left, if it can be said, please don't change a bit!
もう少しだけならまあ踊ってもいいかもな とろけてとろけたいの
If we can keep this up a little longer, let's keep on dancing away, I'm melty-melting into you.
どんなアピールも意味ないし気づいてくれないけれど アタシが寂しい時だけ 逢いにきて！
If I really don't have any appeal, then why do I even try to get you to notice me, so whenever i become so very lonely, please come right away!
全然アタシに興味ないじゅん どこがダメなの？教えてよ(Yeah!)
Although you're not at all interested in me is there anything bad about me? Then just tell me so (Yeah!)
やっぱりアタシに興味ないじゅん 携帯ばかりいじってさ
Totally, you're not at all interested in me, as you keep playing with the buttons on your cell
そもそもだいだいアタシに興味ないじゅん 少しぐらい期待させて(もう…)
Really, really, definitely you're not at all interested in me, although my expectations might be a bit much (More!)
lonely girl 独り占めてよbaby 振り回さないで！
Lonely girl, without you to hold on, baby don't leave me hanging by a thread!
ねぇ？ maybe melty?
Hey? Maybe melty?
ワン・ツー shall we dance? 踊りましょう
One-two, shall we dance? Yeah give me a show.
早く手と手繋いで 最後にひとつだけ 溺れるくらい愛してよ
Come on and hand, in hand, don't hesitate, and just remember that until the end, I want you to drown me in all your love.
全然アタシに興味ないじゅん キミが好きなのは自分 でしょ(Yeah!)
Although you're not at all interested in me I wonder if you really only love yourself (Yeah!)
やっぱりアタシに興味ないじゅん その話もう聞き飽きたわ
Totally, you're not at all interested in me, but I've grown tired of that dumb fairytale.
そもそもだいだいアタシに興味ないじゅん そーやってまた誤魔化して… (もう!) get the last dance 覚悟はできてるの？ 気まぐれメルシー
Really really, definitely you're not at all interested in me, as the gambling cheater says… (More!) Get the last dance, are you ready for more? Kimagure Mercy
ほらほら また始まった
C'mon, c'mon, here we go again
得意の自己弁護言い訳
Another self-serving excuse and defense...
「でもね」「だって」
"But then..." "Because..."
ほらほら また始まった
C'mon, c'mon, here we go again
ごめん！からっぽのキスのパターンって感じ？簡易
Sorry! Is it like an empty kiss pattern? Simple!
いつかアタシだけ そんな夢見たこともあったけど
I even had dreams like that just for myself sometimes
寂しい時だけ電話して もううんざりだわ！
Call me when you're lonely, but now I'm so sick of it!
全然アタシに興味ないじゃん
You're never interested in me at all!
キミが好きなのは自分 でしょ(yeah!)
You only love yourself, right? (Yeah!)
やっぱりアタシに興味ないじゃん
You're still not interested in me at all,
その話もう聞き飽きたわ
And I'm already sick of hearing that story!
そもそもだいたいアタシに興味ないじゃん
Above all, you're not interested in me at all,
そうやってまた誤魔化して… (もう！)
Just like that, twisting things around again... (Gosh!)
be my boy わがまますぎbaby
Be my boy, you're way too selfish, baby!
抱きしめてよね！
Hold me tight, won't you!
ホントキミはしょうもないな
Honestly, you're hopeless...
甘いアタシ「しょうがないな」
Sweet me says, "There's no helping it."
泣いたって行かないでって言ったって変わりゃしないや！
Crying and pleading, "Don't go," but nothing ever changes!
もう少しだけなら踊ってもいいかもな
If it's just a little bit, maybe I could dance with you?
とろけてとろけたいの
Melting away into your sweet honey lies.
どんなアピールも意味ないし気づいてくれないけど
No appeal works and you never even notice, but
アタシが寂しい時だって 逢いにきて！
Come see me when I'm feeling lonely!
全然アタシに興味ないじゃん
You're never interested in me at all!
どこがダメなの？教えてよ(yeah!)
What's wrong with that? Tell me why! (Yeah!)
やっぱりアタシに興味ないじゃん
Still not interested in me at all,
携帯ばかりいじってさ
Fiddling with your phone all the time!
そもそもだいたいアタシに興味ないじゃん
Still not interested in me at all,
少しくらい期待させて(もう…)
At least let me have a little hope... (Geez...)
lonely girl 独り占めしてよbaby
Lonely girl, take all of me, baby!
振り回さないで！
Don't look away from me!
ねえ？maybe melty?
Hey, maybe melty?
ワン・ツー shall we dance? 踊りましょ
One, two, shall we dance? Let's move!
はやく手と手繋いで 最後にひとつだけ
Hurry, take my hand and for the very last time,
溺れるくらい愛してよ
Love me till I drown in it!
全然アタシに興味ないじゃん
You're never interested in me at all!
キミが好きなのは自分 でしょ(yeah!)
You only love yourself, right? (Yeah!)
やっぱりアタシに興味ないじゃん
You're still not interested in me at all,
その話もう聞き飽きたわ
And I'm already sick of hearing that story!
そもそもだいたいアタシに興味ないじゃん
Above all, you're not interested in me at all,
そうやってまた誤魔化して… (もう！)
Just like that, twisting things around again... (Gosh!)
語り合って家族はできてるの
Family is already taking care of it...
get the last dance 覚悟はできてるの？
Get the last dance, are you ready for this?
気まぐれメルシィ
Capricious Mercy...
…味はいかが？
...What kind of taste is it?
(愛とは不思議な) 今から紡ぐ物語...
(Love is a mysterious thing...) A story weaving together from now on...
愛という名のハンバーガー
A hamburger named love,
私は恋を夢見る アメリカンガール
I'm an American girl dreaming of romance.
大好きな食べ物はハンバーガー
My favorite food is a hamburger!
ああ～愛しいのダーリンどこにいるの...
Ah, where is my beloved darling...?
恋とは何か?考えてみよう
What is love like? Let's think about it.
ふわふわ あつあつ
Fluffy and piping hot,
これはまるでトーストバンス!!
just like toasted buns!!
好きとは何か?感じてみたいの
What does love feel like? I want to feel it.
赤く 甘ずっぱい それはまるでトマトケチャップ!!
Very red and bittersweet, just like tomato ketchup!!
理想のダーリンはシャキシャキレタス
My ideal darling has crunchy lettuce,
それであってパワフルなハンバーグ ステキ
and a powerful hamburger steak. Delicious!
でもなんだかほらお腹すいたわ お料理しちゃおうそうしよう!!
But somehow, look, my stomach is rumbling! Let's cook!
(チャレンジ)じんわりこんがりバンズを
(Challenge) Gradually brown the buns!
(お絵かき)きんとケチャップでぬれば
(Drawing) Coat them with ketchup!
(バッチグー)具にはレタスとビーフパティ
(Batchiguru) Top the beef patty with lettuce!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
ステキ i like hamburger
Wonderful, I like hamburger!
(完成)いいね!!上手にできました!
(Complete) Yay! I made it perfectly!
(ただでも)もう何か足りないようなの
(And yet) Something still feels missing...
(悩んで)でもシンプルが一番ね
(Worrying) But simplicity is best!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
baby!! ai like hamburger
大好き好きよハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
I love, love hamburgers!
大好き好きよハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
さあいただきましょう!!ハンバーガー
So let's dig in right now!! Hamburger!
みつめるだけでどきどきする...
Just staring at you makes my heart race...
伝えきれぬもりかみしめる幸せ
The warmth conveyed, the joy of cherishing it.
ああ～私のダーリン誰ですか...
Ah~ Who could my darling be...?
デートをしたいな♪なんておもってたの
I wanted to go on a date ♪ I was thinking just that.
ねえおもうだけで
Hey, just thinking about it,
チーズのようにとろけそう
I feel like I'll melt away just like cheese!
でも時間がきたらバイバイは嫌だよ
But when time's up, I hate saying goodbye!
もうはなさかないで
Don't let go of me anymore,
オニオンみたい涙がでちゃう
Tears pouring out like onions!
デートのコースはドライブがいい
A drive would be the best course for a date,
目立ち焼きな太陽浴びて
Basking in the sunny, egg-like sun,
き・ら・り☆
Spa-rk-le ☆
時にあまくて時に刺激がいい
Sometimes sweet, sometimes stimulating is good!
バターとマスタードおお願い!!
Butter and mustard, please!!
(アレンジ)じわりとろ～りチーズと
(Arrange) Slowly melting cheese with...
(こうとう)オニオン目玉焼き追加で
(Addition) Extra onions and a fried egg!
(できれば)バターとマスタードぬって
(If possible) Butter and mustard spread!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
きらり♪ i like hamburger
Sparkle ♪ I like hamburger!
(完璧)きれいにちゃんとできました!
(Perfection) I made it cleanly and properly!
(ただでも)もうボリュームありすぎだわ
(And yet) But the volume is way too big!
(私と)隣で一緒に食べてよ
(With me) Eat it together right next to me!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
come on!! ai like hamburger
大好き好きよハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
I love, love hamburgers!
大好き好きよハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
さあいただきましょう!!だけど
So let us dig in right now!! But wait—
やっぱりダーリンと食べたいなァ!
I still want to eat it with my darling!
(チャレンジ)じんわりこんがりバンズを
(Challenge) Gradually brown the buns!
(お絵かき)きんとケチャップでぬれば
(Drawing) Coat them with ketchup!
(バッチグー)具にはレタスとビーフパティ
(Batchiguru) Top the beef patty with lettuce!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
ステキ i like hamburger
Wonderful, I like hamburger!
(アレンジ)じわりとろ～りチーズと
(Arrange) Slowly melting cheese with...
(こうとう)オニオン目玉焼き追加で
(Addition) Extra onions and a fried egg!
(できれば)バターとマスタードぬって
(If possible) Butter and mustard spread!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
きらり♪ i like hamburger
Sparkle ♪ I like hamburger!
大好き好きよハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
I love, love hamburgers!
大好き好きよハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
さあいただきましょう!!
So let us dig in right now!!
エブリデイハンバーガーを食べましょう!!
Everybody, let's eat hamburgers!
大好き好きハンバーガー
I really love, love hamburgers!
baby!! ai like hamburger
おなかいっぱいこころもいっぱい
My stomach is full, my heart is full too!
愛という名ハンバーガー
A hamburger named love,
ごちそうさま☆
Thank you for the meal ☆
どぅわ♪
Doo-wop ♪
愛とは不思議な
(Love is such a mysterious thing...)
いまから紡ぐ物語...
Now beginning the story...
愛という名のハンバーガー
A hamburger called "love"
私は恋を夢見るアメリカンガール
I'm an American girl dreaming of romance.
大好きな食べ物はハンバーガー
My absolute favorite food is hamburgers.
あぁ、愛しい手のダーリンどこにいるの...
Ah, my dear darling, where could you be...?
恋とは何かな？考えてみよう
What exactly is love like? Let me ponder it for a bit.
ふわふわ　あっつあっつ　それはまるでトーストバンズ！！
Fluffy, fluffy, and piping hot, it's just like toasted buns!!
好きとは何かな？感じてみたいの
What does being in love feel like? I want to experience it.
赤く甘酸っぱい　それはまるでトマトケチャップ！！
Very red and bittersweet, it's just like tomato ketchup!!
理想のダーリンはシャキシャキレタス　それでいてパワフルなハンバーグステーキ
My ideal darling is like crunchy lettuce, and yet powerful like a hamburger.
でもなんだかほらおなかスイタワ　お料理しちゃおうそうしよう！！
And yet, look, my tummy is rumbling, so let's put on our aprons and cook!
（そうしよう！！）
(Let's do it!!)
（チャレンジ）じんわりこんがりバンズを
(Challenging...) Gradually toast the buns till they're brown enough,
（お絵かき）きんとケチャップで塗って
(Drawing) Spread the ketchup over it just like this,
（バッチグー）具にはレタスとビーフパティ
(Perfect!) Place some lettuce and a beef patty inside.
大好き大好きハンバーガー　ステキ i like hamburger
I really love, love hamburgers, wonderful i like hamburger.
（完成）いいね！！綺麗にできました！！
(Complete) Great!! I cooked it perfectly!
（ただでも）もうなにか足りないような
(And yet) But somehow it feels like something's missing,
（悩んで）でもシンプルが一番ね
(Worrying) But then I guess simple is the best for me.
大好き大好きハンバーガー　baby！！ ai like hamburger
I really love, love hamburgers, baby!! ai like hamburger.
大好き大好きよハンバーガー　さあいただきましょう！！
I really, really love hamburgers, so let us dig in right now!!
みつめるだけできゅんきゅんする…
Just gazing at you makes my heart race...
伝わるぬくもりかみしめる幸せ
Feeling the warmth passed on, savoring the happiness.
あぁ私のダーリン誰ですか…
Ah~ Who is my darling...?
デートをしたいな♪なんて思ってたの　ねぇおもうだけで
I was thinking, "I'd love to go on a date ♪" Hey, just thinking about it
チーズのようにとろけそう
Makes me melt away like cheese.
よおいよいよおいよいよおいよいよおー！！！
Yoooooooooo!
寿限無　寿限無　五劫の擦り切れ
Jugemu jugemu, five-phase expiration...
笑おう　笑おう　さあ笑いましょう　こんな時代こそ笑いましょう
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh! Life may be hard, but let's laugh.
笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）泣いたら負けだ　やけくそ笑いましょう
Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) If you cry, you lose! So just laugh until your sides ache!
波乱万丈　酸いも甘いも乗り越えた　あっぱれ日本人
Life may have its ups and downs, but the great Japanese can get over it.
笑おう　どんな時でも　ナニクソ笑いましょう
Laugh! Whatever time may bring, laugh until you run out of breath.
がっはっは　にゃっほっほ　空気なんて読まずに笑っとけ
Ha ha ha, bwa ha ha, who cares where you are? Just laugh!
笑顔　笑顔　笑う門には福来る
Smile, smile! Smile and the world will smile back at you!
笑おう　笑おう　笑えなくても　笑うしかないでしょう笑いましょう
Laugh, laugh, even if you can't, you have no choice but to laugh, so let's laugh.
笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）こうかふ上げて　ひたすら笑いましょう
Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) Lifting the corners of your mouth, just laugh your heart out.
おんいにらん　だいききせんさい　くくりかえした　げんだい日本人
Even through great famines and crises, modern Japanese have pushed through.
笑おう　未来へいこう　ぐはぐはと笑いましょう
Laugh into the infinite future, let's laugh out loud "Gu haha".
小娘のたわごとと切り捨てないで　しかめ面なんか変な顔
Don't dismiss it as a young girl's idle talk, making scowling faces looks weird.
笑顔を見たいから　笑おう　笑おう　さあ笑いましょう
Because I want to see your smile, laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh!
こんな時代こそ笑いましょう　笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）泣いたら負けだ
Life may be hard, but let's laugh! Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) If you cry, you lose!
やけくそ笑いましょう　波乱万丈
So just laugh until your sides ache! Life may have its ups and downs,
酸いも甘いも乗り越えた　あっぱれ日本人　笑おう　どんな時でも
but the great Japanese can get over it. Laugh! Whatever time may bring,
ナニクソ笑いましょう　はらうんじょう　すいもあまいも
laugh until you run out of breath. Just laugh your heart out,
のりこえた　あっぱれ日本人　笑おう　どんなときでも
ha ha ha, bwa ha ha, who cares where you are? Just laugh!
なにクソ笑いましょう　がっはっは　にゃっほっほ
Smile, smile! Smile and the world will smile back at you!
空気なんて読まずに笑っとけ　笑顔笑顔　笑う門には福来る
Laugh, laugh, even if you can't, you have no choice but to laugh, so let's laugh.
笑おう笑おう　笑えなくても　笑うしかないでしょう笑いましょう
Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) Lifting the corners of your mouth, just laugh your heart out.
笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）こうかふ上げて　ひたすら笑いましょう
Even through great famines and crises, modern Japanese have pushed through.
おんいのらん　だいぎきせんさい　くりかえした　げんだい日本人
Laugh into the infinite future, let's laugh out loud "Gu haha".
笑おう　未来へいこう　ぐはぐはと笑いましょう
Don't dismiss it as a young girl's idle talk, making scowling faces looks weird.
小娘のたわごとと切り捨てないで　みなさま今天是ようこそおいでいただきました
Because I want to see your smile, everyone, thank you kindly for coming today!
ここで一席！ねずみの娘がよめにいって、じぎにかえってきたんで、
Here is a little story! A rat's daughter got married,
ねずみのお母さんがたいへんおこって、
but soon came back home. The rat's mother got furious and asked,
「あんなにいいところへ、おまえつっついいだ、だれがいいやででてきたんだい？」
"You married into such a nice place, who on earth made you leave?"
「いいえ、だれもいやじゃなんですけど、ごいんきょさんがやさしくていやなの」
"Well, it's not that anyone was bad or anything..."
「やさしいならけっこうじゃないかね」「でも、ねこなでごえですもの」
"Isn't it good if he's kind?" "Yes, but he speaks in a cat-like voice..."
いそがしさにみをまかせて　きえていくようなんてべらんめえ！
Throwing yourself away just because you're busy, don't talk nonsense like that!
笑おう　笑おう　笑えなくても　笑うしかないでしょう笑いましょう
Laugh, laugh, even if you can't, you have no choice but to laugh, so let's laugh.
笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）こうかふ上げて　ひたすら笑いましょう
Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) Lifting the corners of your mouth, just laugh your heart out.
おんのらん　だいききせんさい　くりかえした　げんだい日本人
Even through great famines and crises, modern Japanese have pushed through.
笑おう　未来へいこう　ぐはぐはと笑いましょう
Laugh into the infinite future, let's laugh out loud "Gu haha".
小娘のたわごとと切り捨てないで　しかめ面なんか変な顔
Don't dismiss it as a young girl's idle talk, making scowling faces looks weird.
笑顔を見たいから　笑おう　笑おう　さあ笑いましょう
Because I want to see your smile, laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh!
こんな時代こそ笑いましょう　笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）泣いたら負けだ
Life may be hard, but let's laugh! Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) If you cry, you lose!
やけくそ笑いましょう　波乱万丈
So just laugh until your sides ache! Life may have its ups and downs,
酸いも甘いも乗り越えた　あっぱれ日本人　笑おう　どんな時でも
but the great Japanese can get over it. Laugh! Whatever time may bring,
ナニクソ笑いましょう　がっはっは　にゃっほっほ
laugh until you run out of breath. Just laugh your heart out,
空気なんて読まずに笑っとけ　笑顔笑顔　笑う門には福来る
ha ha ha, bwa ha ha, who cares where you are? Just laugh!
笑おう　笑おう　笑えなくても　笑うしかないでしょう笑いましょう
Smile, smile! Smile and the world will smile back at you!
笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）こうかふ上げて　ひたすら笑いましょう
Laugh, laugh, even if you can't, you have no choice but to laugh, so let's laugh.
おんのらん　だいききせんさい　くりかえした　げんだい日本人
Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) Lifting the corners of your mouth, just laugh your heart out.
笑おう　未来へいこう　ぐはぐはと笑いましょう
Even through great famines and crises, modern Japanese have pushed through.
小娘のたわごとと切り捨てないで　しかめ面なんか変な顔
Laugh into the infinite future, let's laugh out loud "Gu haha".
笑顔を見たいから　笑おう　笑おう　さあ笑いましょう
Don't dismiss it as a young girl's idle talk, making scowling faces looks weird.
こんな時代こそ笑いましょう　笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）泣いたら負けだ
Because I want to see your smile, laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh!
やけくそ笑いましょう　波乱万丈
Life may be hard, but let's laugh! Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) If you cry, you lose!
酸いも甘いも乗り越えた　あっぱれ日本人　笑おう　どんな時でも
So just laugh until your sides ache! Life may have its ups and downs,
ナニクソ笑いましょう　がっはっは　にゃっほっほ
but the great Japanese can get over it. Laugh! Whatever time may bring,
空気なんて読まずに笑っとけ　笑顔笑顔　笑う門には福来る
laugh until you run out of breath. Just laugh your heart out,
笑おう　笑おう　笑えなくても　笑うしかないでしょう笑いましょう
ha ha ha, bwa ha ha, who cares where you are? Just laugh!
笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）こうかふ上げて　ひたすら笑いましょう
Smile, smile! Smile and the world will smile back at you!
おんのらん　だいききせんさい　くりかえした　げんだい日本人
Laugh, laugh, even if you can't, you have no choice but to laugh, so let's laugh.
笑おう　未来へいこう　ぐはぐはと笑いましょう
Laugh (Yeah! Yeah!) Lifting the corners of your mouth, just laugh your heart out.
小娘のたわごとと切り捨てないで　しかめ面なんか変な顔
Even through great famines and crises, modern Japanese have pushed through.
笑顔を見たいから　笑おう　笑おう　さあ笑いましょう
Laugh into the infinite future, let's laugh out loud "Gu haha".
こんな時代こそ笑いましょう　笑おう（ソイヤ　ソイヤ）泣いたら負けだ
Don't dismiss it as a young girl's idle talk, making scowling faces looks weird.
やけくそ笑いましょう　波乱万丈
Because I want to see your smile, laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh!
ヨ〜ッ!!
Yo!!
寿限無寿限無 五劫の擦り切れ
Live long, live long and prosper,
海砂利水魚の水行末 雲来末 風来末
may great wealth await you wherever you go,
食う寝る処に住む処
may you always have your daily bread!
やぶ小路の藪柑子
And always be brimming full of life,
パイポパイポ パイポのシューリンガン
like the long-lived king Shuringan...
Hello, I'm your last brain cell here to tell you it's time to pick up the pencil.
Your exam is due in less than an hour, and what are you doing?
You're watching a 3D shark sing songs to you.
But now you're wondering, is this a dinosaur or is this a shark? I don't really know.
Well, instead of pondering that answer, maybe you should be focusing on your schoolwork.
Thank you for chatting with me. This has been your last brain cell speaking.
We're supposed to turn this into like a fine powder and it's not working.
I don't have a rolling pin. I don't have anything.
Just my my sheer run, my gaming grip.
Use the pan?
Pwing pom pwing pwing pwing pwing!
Today, I'm going to be telling you all about acrylic nails.
Yaaas, girl, I sleep. Yeah, this is like, this is how it needs to be.
I don't think so. I don't think so.
Minna, zombies, and new friends, welcome to Gura's Quiz Show!
It is not a math prison cell.
Shall we begin?
Okie, okie, okie, okie. Let us begin.
First question, please. And I know I'm going to get correct.
First question, please. And I know I'm going to get it correct.
8. Answer: 3 + 5 = 8.
Yes, of course. Yes, of course. Did you doubt me? No. Good, okay.
Next question.
9 times 9.
Wait, there's the finger thing. Do the finger thing, Gura. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Wait, that doesn't look right. I'm going to trust it anyway. 51!
The finger thing never fails. Ow. Wait, where did that come from?
Wait, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7... 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9. I have 9 feet. 10 fingers. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Why did I say 51? 81! 81!
Okay, you see, I decided a little laps in brain judgment, there is nothing wrong with that right cameraman, there is nothing wrong with that.
Okay, you see, I displayed a little lapse in brain judgment. There is nothing wrong with that, right, cameraman? There is nothing wrong with that.
Can I have the next question please? I'm already ready.
I think I got it.
Okay, 54 minus 16. Uh, 54 minus 10 is 44.
44 minus 6... 321 30 29 28... Hi! 28!
44 minus 6... 3, 2, 1, 30, 29, 28... Hi! 28!
I actually got that one. Wait, wait, wait, wait. 54 minus 10. 54 minus 10. 54 minus 10. Oh, is 44 minus 6.
44, 43, 42, 41, 40, 39, the... Hi! 38!
44, 43, 42, 41, 40, 39, 38... Hi! 38!
See? It's not so bad, is it, huh? No, this little heavy piling up next to me is not so bad, is it?
See? It's not so bad, is it, huh? No, this little heap piling up next to me is not so bad, is it?
Can I have the next question? I'm on a roll.
Um, can I use Pemdas? Pemdas is parentheses. Pemdas. 3 + 5, 3 + 2, oh, and 3 + 2 is 5 * 17 is...
Um...
Wait, 17 times 5...
5 times 7 is... 5 times 7 is 40...
5 times 7 is 4... 17 times...
I don't remember how to do short hand multiplication.
I don't remember how to do shorthand multiplication.
This is actually terrible.
They said it wasn't going to get these questions right and I told them that I was going to get it right,
They said I wasn't going to get these questions right, and I told them I was going to get it right,
but it looks like I'm not going to get it right now.
but it looks like I'm not going to get it right.
There's shrimp flying everywhere.
Now there's shrimp flying everywhere.
5 times 17 is...
31?
105?
Okay, looks like we're back to the drawing board.
17 times 5...
17, I'm going to write it out.
17 times 5... 5 times 7...
I believe is...
I'll say it's 35, carry the one, 5 times 1 is 5, 6, 7, 8...
85.
I could've sworn I did that right.
Am I forgetting how to do longhand multiplication or is it shorthand multiplication?
I don't know.
5 times 5 is 5, 6, 7, 8... How is this wrong?
How did I get... I can't see with all these shrimp everywhere!
How did I get this wrong? How did I get this wrong?
87?
Can I get a hint? Can I get a hint, please?
No hints?
Okay.
Be that way, then.
Fine.
17 times 2 is...
30? We'll say it's 30 now.
Now it's 30... wait, 5... 6... 7...
80?
What kind of math is that?
I don't understand.
And this is really terrible.
Am I getting this math wrong?
5... Please end this torture! Can I have the next question?
Hint, please!
Go from left to right, in order.
17 times 2...
I'm just doing my math wrong.
17 times 2... 7 times 2 is...
14, but carry the 1... 2, 3... plus...
3 equals...
37!
Yeah! Take that!
Okay...
6... um...
6 times 20 is...
6 times 2 is 12.
So 6 times 20 is... is a... is a 120... oh, god.
So 6 times 20 is... is a... is 120... oh, god.
Is 120 times...
um, minus 9.
6 times 20 is...
6 times 20... 6 times 20... 6 times 2 is 12, so 6 times 20 is 120, right?
Minus 9 is...
Minus 9... 120 minus 9 is 119... is 109!
109... times 13 is...
1,000... Gah!
100... 1,000... 1,000... 1,130?
Okay...
9... 120 minus 9 is 119, times 13 is... 109 minus 13...
109 minus 13 is... Um, why are the shrimp getting bigger and taller and higher?
There's the constant chicken has not been helping!
The constant chicken has not been helping!
120 minus 9... 20... 120... 19, 18, 17, 16, 15, 14, 13, 12, 11...
Oh, okay, it's 111. 111 times 13 is...
1,113!
Was that what the answer was?
Ah!
Wait! Okay! Okay! Okay!
Wait, no, it's 111.
111 minus times 13...
Wait, what is that? 111 times 13 is...
High!
1,213!
1,000... High!
1,412!
It's not even waiting for me to get the answer wrong.
I mean, right. High!
1,604!
20 minus 9 is 11, 11 times 6 is 66, times 13...
See, that's an entirely different math equation now.
Thanks, math guy. Could've used that about 40 minutes ago, now I made a fool of myself in front of everybody.
Wait, what did I say before? 20 minus...
Now they just changed the answer, they said multiplication first.
Little guy in my ear, doesn't seem to be getting his information right.
6 times 2... 20. No, wait, it is.
Oh, wait, I got it, I got it. 6 times 20 is 100... wait, no, 6 times 20 is...
Oh, this is really embarrassing. 120... um, 9 times 13 is... let me dwell on... 9 times 13...
Wait, did I do that right? 9... 10... 11, 111...
10,020!
I think I need... I think I guess I got to get another hint.
120 minus...
104!
like Su usually
Um, okay, is like, you know
reading can like really, really help you, you know?
have like a way better vocabulary.
Bla bla bla bla bla...
Are you looking for a delightful getaway in the deep forests of the unknown souls?
Well, do I have the perfect vacation home for you?
Locked away 3,000 miles in the deep woods, where no one will hear you scream.
The mushroom kings await for your great return.
They prepare a feast for you, or maybe you're the feast.
All right, so that wraps up all the games and quizzes for today.
What did you guys think? どうでしたか？
What did you guys think? How was it?
楽しかった！ ありがとうございます！
It was fun! Thank you very much!
ありがとうございました！ 楽しかったです！
Thank you very much! It was fun!
楽しかった！ ありがとうございます！ 楽しかったです！
It was fun! Thank you very much! It was fun!
Yeah! That was... that was... that was really fun.
I hope we can do this again. また遊びに来てください。
I hope we can do this again. Please come play again.
はーい！ また来まーす！ よろこんで！
Yeah! We'll come again! With pleasure!
Tchah, well, I guess that's it for today's program.
Thanks everyone for tuning in! Thank you everybody for watching!
I hope you had fun too, and I guess we will see...
you guys
uh next time, if we have an episode, yeah?
やばいよ！
No way!
お前！
Hey, you!
美味しくないです！
It doesn't look tasty!
かわいい！
Cute!
Hi everyone,
it's the Gura Shoulder Bag, oh my god!
With very sharky embroideries, matching none other than me, Gawr Gura!
A jacquard weave shoulder strap, which is very trendy and very cool, my man.
Wants you to try it and include it.
Wanted you to try it and include it.
The inside fabric actually matches that of my vintage casual outfit, the very cool patterned pattern, yeah?
The inside fabric actually matches that of my vintage casual outfit, with a very cool pattern, yeah?
Patterned button.
Pattern button!
This bag is perfectly sized for your books or other small belongings,
as well as perhaps your very own gar boost drink.
All right, that's all for me, folks.
Goodbye!
This program was made possible by contributions to Gura from viewers like you.
3D Showcase
[Title: 3D Showcase]